[сверчков стрекот]
[Сова ухает]
[ Phone Rings ]
Hello. [ Man's Voice ]
Wanna have a little fun ?
Who's this ?
Tell me your name and I'll tell you mine.
I don't think so.
[ Farts ]
What's that noise ?
Oops. I farted.
I didn't think you would hear me. No,
that (хлопающий, глотать, появляться) noise.
Oh. I'm making popcorn.
I'm getting ready to watch a video.
Ooh. What is it?
It's just a scary movie.
Do you like scary movies ?
Mm-hmm.
What's your favourite ?
Mm, I don't know.
Think.
Oh, I know.
Um, Kazaa the one where Shaq plays a genie.
That's not a ужастик movie. Well, you haven't
seen Shaq (номер, выступление, игра).
[ Popping ]
Hey, you have a nice voice.
Thanks.
You never did tell me
your name.
Why do you
wanna know my name ?
'Cause I wanna know
who I'm looking at.
What...
What did you say ?
Nice breasts.
Look, what do you want ?
Я хочу увидеть,
как выглядят твои внутренности.
Well... Well, then,
turn to page 54.
Oh.
Hey, nice.
Listen, asshole, you've had your fun, now you
better stop or (иначе, еще, другой, никого, кроме).
Or else what? Or else my boyfriend's
gonna be here any minute,
and he's black
and he'll kick your ass.
Oh, really ?
Yeah.
You mean the one who надевает
макияж and dresses like a woman ?
How did you know ?
Turn the porch lights on.
Help ! Help !
Oh, that's not my boyfriend. I mean, I've
fucked him a couple of times, but that's it.
- [визжание]
- Look, I'm calling the cops.
Go вперед.
Call the cops.
But you (возможно, может) wanna
check the back door first.
You forgot to lock it.
[дверной звонок звенит (колокольчики)]
Take that, you psycho!
[стон
I can't feel my legs.
I think
my arm is broken.
- Sorry.
- I want my mommy.
Hello, Drew.
Oh, God!
[Screams]
- Daddy! Daddy!
- Ugh!
Daddy!
- Daddy!
- [Groans]
Daddy, no! No!
Did you hear something?
No, I didn't hear anything.
[клавиатура щелканье]
[шорох, шелест, шуршание]
[Screams] Bobby, what are you doing?
My dad's in the other room.
It just произошло to me. I never забирался на
(через, посредством, путем, благодаря) your window before.
Now that you got it out of your
system, Bobby, you have to leave.
Why?
Shh. Come on.
What's going on in there ?
Ow ! Daddy's head is (застряла, тупик).
(вытащить, отклеить) Daddy's head.
[стонет]
Dad, can you knock?
Knock? I thought I heard screaming in here.
No. No, you didn't, Dad.
Well, it could've been that (крэк - курительный
какаин, трещина, щель) I smoked earlier, I guess.
Yeah.
Yeah, that's what it was.
Listen. I gotta leave town
for a couple of days.
No big deal. Just that new business I
started with those Colombian guys ?
Oh, you mean Uncle Escobar.
Yeah. Yeah, that's right.
Well, there's a problem.
Some money went пропали.
And (очевидно, видимо, наверное),
some legs are gonna get broken.
It's just better if I lay
low for a couple of days.
If the cops (набег, обыск,
облава) the place... I never heard of you.
And don't forget...
To смыть your (заначку, тайничок).
Oh, you are my little girl.
I love you so much...
that I оставил (лево) you a little
something in the coffee банке.
Dad... But you have to remember
to step on it before you sell it.
Now, what are you gonna (сократить,
доля,отрезать) it with? Um, пекарная...
Пекарная сода.
Not baking (порошок,порох, пудра, присыпка).
Because baking powder guys will have
кексы вырастают out of their nose.
You love that joke,
don't you, honey ?
You've loved that joke
(с тех пор, псолетак как, ибо) you were two years old.
Okay, well...
Okay, I love you.
I love you.
Have a good trip.
Bye.
Bye. Воу!
Is the (берег, горизонт, курсировать,
двигаться по инерции) clear ?
Oh, Cindy, that ночная рубашка.
That was тесный, близкий, закрытый.
God !
I was, uh, home watching The Exorcist,
and it got me thinking about you.
If this is about the time I (стошнило, вырвало) green
слизь and masturbated with a (распятие, крестик)...
It was
my first (пиво, бочка) party, Bobby.
No. No. Uh, it was отредактировано for TV.
All the good stuff was cut out.
So you thought you would just
climb through my window...
and we would
play bump-bump ?
I was kind of надеялся
to get my balls licked,
but I wouldn't wanna break your little
нижнего белья rule, now, would I ?
So maybe just some on-top-of-the-clothes
type (вещь, штука, дело, материал)?
Okay.
But just for a minute.
** [Soft Rock]
What the...
Wrong (набор, свод, установить).
*
Bobby ! Oh, Bobby !
* I don't wanna wait
for our lives to be over **
No, Bobby, don't.
Ow!
Jeez.
(нет вторжению, нарушению границ)
Yeah, my dad.
Okay, (жеребец, гвоздик, конюшни, шип, запонка),
you have to go now.
Oh, um,
about the sex stuff ?
I was only half serious. I don't wanna
(торопить, бежать, лихорадка) you or anything.
Hey, would you (разрешение, урегулирование)
for PG-13 ?
What's that ?
Oh, jeez !
[ Crash ]
Good night, Bobby.
[ Laughing ]
Shorty, you are so громкий.
И убедись you take
your (задницу, сзади, после, в прошлом) to class today.
I do be going to class.
Lunch is not a class, Shorty.
It is when you got
the (голод, закуска, обкурившийся старшеклассник).
See, that's why you such a dumb-ass.
Your mother.
You my brother.
That's your mother too, jackass.
Oh, yeah.
Well, then, your father's stupid.
So ? I don't know him.
Yeah, me тоже, никто.
Hey, girl, you ready ?
Yeah, in a minute.
- Come on. We're gonna be late.
- Wait. There's Buffy.
[кряхтит] I don't know why
you hang out with her.
She is such a ho.
Why do you say that ?
'Cause I've seen her.
My friend Sean had a pool party this summer.
Sean ?
You know, Puff Daddy ?
Anyway,
everybody was drinking Шампанское "Кристалл".
And then it started to get wild, and people were
getting чумовой, чокнутый in the pool and stuff.
I look over and there was your girl getting (брыкалась,
доллар, самец, маркер, отвественность) wild in the Jacuzzi.
So ?
With a поддержка, подмога dancer.
I mean, that's мерзко.
That's-That's lower
than the security guard.
At least security can get you за кулисы
(зад сцены). She don't love herself.
Bye, Daddy. I don't know.
I think Buffy's sweet, Brenda.
She is as подделка
as накладные nails.
Hey, baby girl !
What is up,
my sister ?
- Bye, Mr Gilmore.
- Bye !
Is he gone ?
Yep.
* Do you like what you see
* It's all about the money *
[ Girl ]
Hey, Cindy !
I love this colour.
Let me see that.
Oh, you guys should not use this brand.
Why not ?
Because they test their products on animals.
So ?
Look, have you seen what they do to those (бедный,
плохой, низкий, слабый, несчастный, неимущий) animals ?
Well, I am much more
of a people person.
I'd like to feed all the hungry,
little children of the world.
I'd much rather help my
fellow man than some animal.
Пожалейте (лишний, свободный) dollar ? Get away from
me, you (бомж, бродяга, бездельник, попрошайка) !
Buffy ! Can't you see
he's just hungry ?
Here you go, sir.
A nice sandwich for you.
- See ?
- I said a dollar, bitch !
Ow !
God.
Look at this place.
It's a circus.
Hello. I'm Gail Hailstorm,
author of the book, You're Dead, I'm Rich.
A small college town
is in shock...
after the немыслимое
has happened:
a (жестокий, грубый, зверский) убийство серийное (загул)
that left one teen dead...
That's it.
Two teens dead... [ Gunshot ]
and this small town
потрясен and всколыхнут (смешан).
It's times like these... Police are прочесывают
the area for (подсказки, улики, зацепки, следы).
There are no свидетелей (доступный,
в состоянии, имеющий силу, наличие) at this time.
There are no suspects
in заключении.
Police are asking anyone
to come (направить, вперед) (дать показания).
Reporting live for Black TV. White (люди, друзья,
ребята) are dead and we're getting the на хрен of here !
Grab your shit and let's go,
motherfucker !
Hey, do you think the press
is gonna wanna talk to us ?
Oh, girl, no. The press only wants to interview the most
(невежественный, тупой, необразованный) person they can find.
I'm on TV ! Oh, shit !
First Cops, now this !
Oh, man, I'm gonna be
a star, son !
What can you tell us about Drew ?
Well, she had the класная ass.
I mean, it was like (взрыв, бум, удар, выстрел,
стук)! How close were you to the victim ?
Real close.
Until the (рогипнол, снотворного) больше не действует, отпускает.
Then she woke up talking about выдвигать
обвинения (неотложном обвинении (расход)).
So I just вытащил my язык
out of her ass and left.
What would have были
your last words to Drew ?
Run, bitch ! Run !
Hey, yo, dawg. Does this shirt make me (вид,
взгляд, смотреть, казаться) gay ?
No, man.
What about now ?
Nah. Yeah.
Cool ?
Here. Take one, guys.
Don't forget: выборы Tuesday.
"Don't forget:
election's Tuesday."
Ah ! Goddam it !
Son of a bitch !
What's the (вопрос, дело, материя, проблема, предмет),
honey ?
My отчёт, рапорт card (табель успеваемости).
Well, at least
you got one "A."
Yeah. I did, huh ?
You're so smart.
[ стонет ]
Hey, has anybody seen Bobby ?
Nah.
You know what ?
That kid is always late.
I don't get it.
He lives so close.
** [ Rock ]
See you later,
волосатый Mama, Bubba, Jim,
Big Jim, Little Jim,
Slim Jim, everybody.
I'll see you later.
Ciao, Ding. All right.
Damn, girl.
Mm-mm-mm.
I'd sure like to get in them (штаны,
брюки, трусы). Really ?
Yeah.
What size are these ?
[ Bobby ]
Hey, guys.
Hey, Bobby.
Hey, baby.
How you doing ?
Good.
- You guys see all the reporters out there ?
- Yeah.
Saying that girl Drew Decker
got killed last night.
You know what ?
I think I knew her. Really ?
- She had a brother named Steve ?
- Yeah.
Long hair, pretty little mouth,
perfect ass ?
- That was her.
- Nah, I was talking about Steve.
Whatever happened
to him ?
Do you guys think it's strange
that she got killed...
exactly one year
after we,
you know,
killed that guy ?
Hey, Cindy,
that was an accident.
Was it, Greg ?
[ Greg ]
Yeah !
[ Laughing ]
Would you look
at what they're doing ?
When are we gonna do
stuff like that, huh ?
One day.
You like that, baby ?
Yeah, that's different.
You like that ?
Oh, I love that.
Oh, I love
when you play with my ass.
I'm not playing
with your ass.
Ray !
Oh, my bad.
Come on, man !
Hey, Bobby, (поставь, одень) some music.
Hold on.
Here. Put this on.
* It's дождливые men Yeah,
that's the shit right here !
- * Hallelujah
- * It's raining men
- Baby.
- * Amen
* I'm gonna go out I'm gonna let
myself get * What ? It's a classic.
- * Absolutely промочился влажный *
- Put on the radio, man.
** [ Rock ]
Yeah ! Whoo !
What ? It was (стирка, грязное белье) day.
What the fuck is...
Yeah !
Whoo ! Yeah !
- Hey. Come over here.
- What ?
Just get a little closer to me.
Something you're gonna tell me ?
[ Молния расстегивает] Bobby,
what are you doing ?
I just want you to touch it.
Just touch it. Come on.
Uh... Just a little bit.
Come on.
Whoo !
Ow !
Oh, yeah, that's what I'm talkin' about.
Oh, my God ! Shit !
God, Cindy...
Oh, shit !
[ Ray ] Oh, my God.
What was that ?
I think
we hit something.
Oh, man !
Bobby, look at my car, man !
My dad's чокнится, психанет !
[ Bobby ] I didn't see it.
It вышел of nowhere.
- Oh, my God, we hit a boot.
- Where's the foot ?
I don't know.
Where the...
[крики]
It's a body !
Oh, shit, is he alive ?
I don't know.
- Well, check it out.
- I can't.
- Shit !
- We have to call the police.
No way. I ain't going to jail.
We have to !
Hey Cindy, do you know what they
do to young boys in prison ?
And all those sex-голодные осужденные
just waiting for a fresh piece of meat.
Hey, you're right, Cindy.
Maybe we should call the police.
[ Greg ] Oh, yeah, That's a great idea, Ray.
But what about Brenda, huh ?
You think she wants
to go to jail ?
This is непредумышленное убийство, okay ?
We're all gonna пожаримся for this.
- We're смотрим at 10 to 15 years.
- Shut up, Bobby !
- It's okay. I'm fine.
- Alcohol повсюду. - We're in so much trouble.
I'm fine.
[ Brenda ] Don't вини that shit on me, Ray.
- Look, we'll get избавимся of the body.
- нет необходимости.
-[Brenda] Now you're thinking. -We'll бросим him in the ocean.
-Not the ocean, the (пирс, причал, пристань, бык, столб).
Guess I'll be оставлю, покину now.
[ Greg ] That's a great idea.
- What about the alcohol ?
- We'll get rid of it.
[ Bobby ] Come on.
It'll be all right.
Come on. Hurry up. Let's go. Put him in the
(багажник, сундук, ствол, чемодан, хобот, туловище).
I won't have anything to do with this !
[ Greg ] Shut up !
Cindy, come on. We'll just притворимся,
притендуем it never happened.
You know, like the time we got drunk
and we went down on each other.
I'll get his arm. I'll grab his other arm.
I'll grab his ass.
We'll take him down to Williamson
бухта and we'll бросим him in there.
The sharks'll take care
of the доказательствах.
Oh, my God,
someone's coming.
Oh, shit. It's Shorty.
Brenda, take care of him.
** [ Rap Playing
On Radio ]
Shorty, I know you ничего (разве, мало,
верно) driving without no papers.
I got papers,
траву, кальян,
all the ingredients
to make a high nigga пирог.
Hey, yo, can I help you ?
Yo, what's up, Ray ?
- Yo, son, you all need клемма cables ?
- Nah, we're cool.
Oh, good, 'cause I забыл
my окурочный зажим at home.
- Go home, Shorty.
- Yeah, I-I'll see you later.
Peace, Ray.
- Get the trunk closed.
- [ Buffy ] It won't close.
- I'll do it.
- [ стонет ]
[ Shorty Laughing ]
Hold on. Hold on. Put him down.
He's heavy. Oh, God.
Okay, look. On three we dump him
over the (выступ карниз уступ край).
Wait, wait, wait.
Shouldn't we at least check his бумажник ?
For what ?
Shit, he might have some money.
We already совершили murder.
We might as well обокрасть his ass.
- I'll take the credit cards.
- I want his Бижутерия. - I'm gonna take his трусы, штаны.
[ All кричат ] убираться с !
Hey, yo, get off ! His трусы are mine ! Yo !
[ хихиканье] I got me a gold ring.
Credit cards.
All right, let's get him in the water.
I don't think I can, Greg.
- It's not too late.
- Shut up, okay ?
- Christ, already. I'll do it.
- Come on. Just get him in the water.
Okay. One, two,
three.
Right now we make a pact.
We take this to our могила (серьезный, грубый, тяжелый).
Agreed ?
Agreed. Agreed.
- Agreed ?
- [ Brenda, Bobby ] Agreed.
Say it, Cindy.
Say it !
We take this
to our grave. Say it !
[ рвотные позывы ] We take this to our grave.
Say it.
Greg, (остынь, расслабься).
Come on. You're hurting her.
We take this
to our grave. Ow.
And we never
mention this again.
Mention what ?
- The guy we just killed.
- Well, you just mentioned it, Greg.
Starting now !
Stupid bitch, man.
God. I hate him. It's gonna be okay, baby.
It's gonna be okay.
I promise. Just touch it again.
Come on. Please.
You have to идти дальше, Cindy.
That's all behind us now. Exactly.
It's a случайность.
Greg's right, Cindy.
I mean, what do you think
we're in, a horror movie ?
Yeah, you guys are right.
If we were,
they'd probably (актеры, состав, роль, гипс, тень, слепок,
заклинание) some дура like Jennifer Love Huge Tits to play me.
Yeah, or they'd актеры people in their
late twenties, early thirties to play us.
[ Bell Rings ] Kenny, get the camera ready.
Here. Hold my gum.
Hi. Sheriff, Sheriff, can I get a (заявление
выступление показание)? No comment.
Damn. Who do I have to повалять
дурака here to get a stupid story ?
Hey ! Hey, no running.
[ (сдувает, свисток) свистеть]
Loser.
[ Continues Blowing ]
Slow it down !
[ Boy ] отсосать у меня !
All right !
Hi. Gail Hailstorm.
Field Reporter, Hard Story.
Special Officer Doofy.
Oh, hi, Doofy. Doofy, listen.
Is there a problem on campus ?
No comment. No comment.
Okay. Okay.
You know, you look (ужасно очень
слишком) young to be a police officer.
I'm 25 and a half years old.
Ooh !
Yeah, that's this many.
Ah, so big.
Yeah. That's big.
Well, you don't look a day over 12.
[ смеется ]
(кроме только разве исключая хотя) for the
big head and стеклянный взгляд in your eyes.
Ooh, was that слюна?
Yeah. I забыл to swallow.
Don't worry,
'cause I never forget.
[ Both Laughing ]
[ Farts ]
Would you напомнишь me not to do that again ?
Sorry.
[ Man Over P.A. ] Due to the недавней трагедией,
the sheriff and me, your директор школы (главный),
will be questioning all
students throughout the day.
Wow. Sounds like we've got the задатки
of a serial killer on our hands.
Yeah, I'm not положено to say.
It's official police business.
Hey, Doofy, what do you say you and
I go inside my фургон over there...
and, uh, get to know
each other a little better ?
Would you like that ?
Yeah, that van right there. That van ?
[ Chuckles ]
Yeah.
Yeah, okay, let's go.
Come on. Oh !
A terrible tragedy
and an невыносимая потеря.
It's days like today
that we need молится in school.
It starts to развалить (распутать) the very
moral устоев (ткань, основа) of our society.
Here you go, baby.
Go to your daddy.
Oh !
[ Chuckles ]
I'll see you after class.
Sweet !
All right !
Okay, class, who would like to give
their oral presentation first ?
- Oh !
- Anybody ?
- Yes !
- Anybody else ?
- Okay, Heather.
- [ Students стонет ]
Okay. Can I start ?
Yeah.
Okay, my presentation
is on the First (поправка изменение).
And it began on May 25, 1787 in
Филадельфии with George Washington.
And it гласит (штаты),
and I цитирую,
"When our Founding Fathers утверждали
принятие of our великолепный Constitution..."
[ Heather Continuing ]
The First поправка gives us the
right to say what we want...
Oh, shut the fuck up !
So, who's next ?
[постановки ]
Uh, Cindy Campbell.
Isn't she the daughter
of, well, you know...
Oh, yeah, you know, old миссис, uh...
Old missus...
[ Sheriff ] Yeah.
Yeah, the one and only
The one and only.
[прочищает горло (кашляет)]
Why, hello, Cindy.
Hi, Principal Squiggman.
- Thanks, Doofy.
- It's Special Officer Doofy today, Cind.
Now, Cindy, Sheriff has some questions
that he would like to ask you today.
What is that... god-awful smell ?
I don't know.
I got a poopie.
Did you just say
that you went poopie ?
Yeah. It was good.
[ Sheriff ] Mm.
- Get him out of here.
- Yes.
Thank you, Doofy.
[ Doofy ] Okay.
You should now go back
to Special Ed.
- Okay. отдавать честь.
- Maybe a change of underwear, son.
Bye, Doofy.
Bye, Cind.
How are you, Cindy ?
Fine.
How are you, Sheriff ?
Вздутие, запор.
Got a фурункул (варить) на my ass the size
of a грецкий орех. You know, the usual.
Cindy, I want to ask you some
questions about Drew Decker.
- I didn't really know her.
- Oh, come on. Sure you do.
No. I mean,
I didn't really know her.
я был in this game a long time.
Don't обманывай обманщика.
Tell me about Drew. What
was she like in bed, Cindy ?
Tried to get you.
It's an old police trick.
It's an old police trick. You didn't попала (вина,
осень, гибель, падение) for it. Good for you, kid.
(марш поход поднять увелечение) !
Pass ! Pass !
[ Whistle Blows ] All right,
в душ!
Yes !
Yo, Dugan, man, nice play, yo.
Я одобряю.
Johnson, what
a block, baby.
Word up.
Woodward. Nice ass.
Damn.
Yo, Greg, what's up ? You gonna (попасть,
ударить) the showers or what ?
No, man. I think I'm gonna упражняться
(разрабатывать), beat the bag a little.
как знаешь, kid. All right.
Last one in the shower's a тухлый egg !
Come on, народ!
I'm gonna get народ ! [ Laughing ]
Don't let Uncle Ray
catch you !
Who did this ?
Huh ? Where are you ?
This isn't funny,
all right ?
A small dick's like a (инвалидность
неполноценность недееспособность)!
Would you make fun of a guy in a wheelchair ?
Huh ? Would you ?
Come on out here,
you sick  ублюдок!
I'll kick the shit out of you right now !
All right ?
It's not the size
of the молота (курок, забить),
it's the гвоздь (ноготь, арустовать)
you're бросаешь it at !u
[ Cindy ]
It's a позор жаль how she died.
- She was such a nice girl.
- Yeah, she used to baby-sit my brother Doofy.
- He had the biggest влюбился on her.
- Ray, you're a dead man.
Hey, hey, hey, hey,
hey, hey, hey, hey.
You wanna get
голые задницы и борьба?
- Принести it on (ну давай), Ray !
- Hold my earrings. Where's my Vaseline ?
- Take it easy. What's the problem ?
- I'll show you the problem.
Oh...
That's you ?
They... They turned the hot water
off in the showers, all right ?
Laugh it up, you guys.
Big laugh.
You know what ?
You can all go to hell !
Greg,
you're not the only one who got one.
Oh, you mean
Bobby's got a baby dick too ?
No. I was talking
about the (записка примечание).
I got one too.
Somebody knows.
That's bullshit, Cindy.
Someone's just trying
наебать нас.
We have to call
the police, Greg.
You call the police, and I'll kill you лично.
[удары кулаком Stomach ]
You're hurting her, man.
And you know what ?
That goes
for all of you guys.
That psycho wants
a piece of me, bring it on.
But I'm not going to jail.
You got that ?
[ Cindy Стонет ]
[ Bones хруст, перемалывание ]
[ All Groaning ]
What's everybody
talkin' about ?
Just forget it, Shorty.
You already know too much.
[ Cindy Groaning ]
[ Audience Cheering ] [ Emcee
] Aren't they beautiful ?
Buffy !
[ Man ] конкурсант number one !
Very good.
And contestant number two.
And contestant number three.
[ Greg ]
Buffy ! That's my girl !
- That's my girlfriend !
- Yeah, that's my girlfriend too !
Hey, kiss my ass !
[ Boy #2 ] Yeah, I'm запал that too !
- All right, Buffy !
- Hey, shut the hell up, man !
- [ Boy #3 ] The best тёлка I ever had !
- What, you want a piece of me ?
Now the talent часть доля порция
of the конкуренция конкурс соревнование.
Oh, you guys, I'm gonna go downstairs for
a ближе место. See you after the show.
Number three, Buffy Gilmore.
[ крики и аплодисменты]
Hey, you know what ? I'm gonna сходить в туалет
Ты хочешь чтобы я принес you back anything ?
No, no, no. I'm good, man. But hurry back.
She's gonna (играть выступить).
Don't worry. I'll be back.
Good evening, Buffy.
And what will be
your talent for this вечер?
актёрский игра. I'll be doing
a dramatic reading.
[ Boy ]
Yeah, yeah !
Buffy Gilmore
doing a dramatic reading.
Hey, do that thing from Спасатели Малибу !
She's running down the beach !
Look out, Greg !
Look behind you !
- It's him ! It's the killer !
- Huh ?
Oh, my God !
Somebody do something !
He's killing him !
- He's killing him !
- Must be an original (пьеса, произведение, статья).
He's killing him !
- [рыдание всхлипывание плач]
- She's good. She's good.
- What's wrong with you people ?
- That's fantastic.
You fucking bastards !
Why won't anyone help ?
- Amazing.
- [ Woman ] She's the next Pamela Lee.
Oh, God !
Oh, God ! Don't !
- [ стоны]
- Greg, hold on !
[ведущий конферансье ] Поаплодируйте (сдаться,
отказаться) for Buffy Gilmore ! Beautiful.
- Absolutely fantastic.
- [ Cheering ]
I think we have a winner,
ladies and gentlemen. Miss Buffy Gilmore !
Buffy, wait.
You have to go back on stage.
No. I have to get to Greg.
But you won !
They're calling your name.
There's a killer...
- I won ?
- They're calling your name. Go.
- Buffy, what happened ? What about Greg ?
- Oh, fuck Greg. I won.
Congratulations !
Oh, out of my way, loser !
Miss Buffy Gilmore !
[ Cheers And свистки ]
* Here she comes
* Miss Teen She's So Fine
* Such lovely tits Give me my
корона (обвинение прокурор), bitch.
* And a great позади
* There she is
Doggy style anytime *
* And I'll do her behind
behind and behind *
* Oh, there she is
* She loves 69 *
There's no (знак признак след подпись табличка)
of him anywhere.
He (мог бы, возможно) taken the body.
That's impossible, Cindy.
There's no blood. There's nothing.
Look around. I bet it's just Greg playing...
another one
of his dumb jokes.
He's gonna (появиться прийти). I'm sure of it.
He's probably at my house waiting for us right now,
you guys.
All right, fine.
But you know what ?
I'm gonna look around some more, so...
You возражаешь поймать (подвезти поездку)
home with Buffy ? Yeah, no problem.
All right, fine.
Call me later.
** [жужжание гудение мычание]
[ Phone Rings ]
Hello. [ Man's Voice ] Hello,
Cindy.
Who is this ?
It's me, Bobby.
You know, your boyfriend.
Yeah, I'm sorry. I guess
I'm a little (нервный, на взводе) lately.
Hey, any след, признак of Greg ?
No.
Do you want me to come by ?
I'm just gonna take a bath,
and then I'm gonna go to bed.
Okay. I'd really like to see you, but...
I love you.
Aw.
I love you too, baby.
[ Farts ]
[ Rings ]
Bobby, I told you...
[ Man's Voice ] I still know
what you did last Halloween.
Who is this ?
[ соединяется гудок ]
[ Phone Rings ]
[ Screams ]
[ Стук ]
Ow ! Ow !
[ Ringing ]
Hello.
I'm gonna kill you.
I'm gonna порезать тебя.
Who is this ?
I'm gonna порубить you like печень.
What do you want ?
I'm in the house.
[хихиканье]
Do you know where I am ?
[ Snickering ]
I could be anywhere.
I'm like the ветер (,завести), baby.
Yeah. Where am I ?
[ Snickering ]
Um, you're-you're
behind the диван.
[ Snickering Stops ]
What ? How do you know that ?
I can, um, see your feet.
Ah !
Okay, turn around.
Close your eyes.
No подглядывать.
Yeah. No. No. No.
Hey, no peeking.
No peeking. Turn around.
Good.
Okay, now you look.
Now do you know
where I am ? You don't.
No, Mr Killer.
I don't know where you are.
- I'll give you a big clue.
- [ Screams ]
Oh !
I gotta stop drinking.
Grandma !
Ow, baby !
Oh, my (бедро хип модный шиповник)!
[ Screaming ]
[ Woman диспетчер ] White woman
in trouble off the 744...
[ Sirens воют ]
[ветки щелкают]
[ Screams ]
Are you okay ? I heard screaming.
What's going on ?
- Bobby, he was here.
- Shh.
- The killer was here, Bobby.
- It's okay.
I can explain that.
Oh, my God.
A friend gave (нравятся, к ним) to me.
Cindy. Cindy.
[ Screaming ]
Cindy. Cindy !
Cindy ! Cindy !
Cindy !
It's me, Cind.
[задыхается ]
Cindy, you know me.
Cindy.
I know you've had a тяжелый night,
Cindy, so I won't задержу you.
I just want you to look at some photos.
Tell me what you think.
Mm-mmm.
No ?
No.
I'm sorry, Sheriff.
You sure ?
Okay, you're free to go.
Do you have somebody picking you up ?
Yeah.
Oh. Just...
Just check
that one out again.
Mm, no. No ? No ? Well, стоит попытки (кадр,
укол, пуля, рюмка). All right, thanks.
Guess what I just did with those
hookers we арестовали. No way.
All the way, man ! Yes, yes.
Watch this. Doofy !
- Yeah ?
- Come on. Come on.
Okay.
Special Officer Doofy
reporting.
Hey, Doofy,
smell my fingers.
What's that ? That's when you
know you've become a man, Doofy !
Hey, Terry,
smell my finger.
What the hell is that ?
My ass.
Get the hell out of here, Doofy.
Doofy.
Mom said get home now.
Tell Mom I'm on official police business.
Cindy, are you okay ? Hey, hey, hey.
No talking to the witness.
Go get in the car, Doofy.
She's coming with us. Does Mom know ?
- Yeah, Doofus.
- Mom says when I wear this (значок жетон),
you're supposed to обращаться с me
like a man of the law.
Mom also said for you to stop совать
your dick in the vacuum cleaner.
[ Cheering ] Oh !
Oh !
Okay, three, two...
[ Man ] Oh, no. (боже,
черт возьми) (Проклятие черт). What now ?
It's just that there's all these numbers
with deci... What, can't you считать ?
- No, I can count, but there's really...
- Let me make it easy for you. внимание.
This little свинка went to the market.
This little piggy stayed home.
Now, if this little piggy doesn't свернешь
(список, дробь, булочка) the goddam camera...
- I'm gonna put my foot up his fuckin' ass...
- We're live, Gail.
Gail Hailstorm стоит перед
of the police station...
where I'm going to try and get
a заглянуть of Cindy Campbell,
the young girl who was
attacked ранее this evening.
- You're on my foot, fat shit !
- Sorry, G...
What did I say ?
"Don't ever step on Gail's shoes."
Why not ?
Because Gail wears Prada shoes.
You idiot.
I'm a bad man.
[ Reporters крик ]
Cindy ! Cindy !
Cindy, can we get a заявление?
Buffy Gilmore, Miss Teen.
She's not talking. Is it true the
police have someone in заключении ?
- Come on, Cindy.
- Cindy, your ass looks fat !
Bitch !
Good shot.
Come on.
All right, who сознался a feel ?
Gail, it was me.
Oh, my God.
It was an accident, Gail.
I only touched it,
the top of the грудь.
It was so нежный, мягкий and juicy.
Shut up !
[тональный сигнал готовности к набору номера]
[ Phone Rings ]
- Yo.
- Hello, Shorty. What are you doing ?
Nothin'. Sittin' here watchin' the game.
Smokin' some приятель.
Are you all alone ?
Wassup ?
What the...
Who's that ?
Yo, pick up the phone.
- Wassup ?
Yo, Dookie,
pick up the phone !
- Yo.
- Wassup ?
- What you doin', son ?
- Nothin'. Just расслабляюсь, killin'.
True. True.
So you think
Bobby did it ?
I don't know.
But he was there, Buffy.
I knew there had to be something.
He's just too perfect.
красивый, smart,
good in bed.
- What did you say ?
- Uh...
Hey, Cind. Got your ice (пачка
пакет) for your (рука помощь).
- Ow !
- Sorry.
[ стонет ] I'll get
you one for your head.
No, no, that's okay,
Doofy.
Hey, we're gonna get that guy
you бросили in the water. Yeah.
I'll be next door
if you need me.
Night, Cind.
Buffy, you told him ?
The идиот подслушивал a conversation
Greg and I were having.
- Yeah, but what if he says something ?
- Who's gonna believe...
a отсталый тормоз (умственно)
like him anyway? Don't worry.
Cindy, telephone.
Thank you.
Hello. [ Man's Voice ] Hello,
Cindy.
(полагать угадать похоже) what.
No !
You got the wrong guy.
Doofy !
It's not Bobby.
Who is this ?
[ Dial Tone ]
Doofy ! Doofy !
Oh, my God.
Hello ?
I said don't беспокоить меня
while I'm cleaning my room !
I heard Bobby вышел
this morning.
I haven't seen him рядом.
Is he сердится?
You mean (поскольку, с тех пор) you заклеймила
him the drug dealer? No. His heart is broken.
Yo, son. It's like
I seen this all before.
They had a killer at your old high school,
Shorty ?
No, it was
in this movie Scream.
Same dialogue and everything.
This is (плохо, болезни).
How did it end ?
I don't know.
Some niggas started shooting up in the movie
theatre, so we just (сбежали началась вспыхнули).
No сомнение.
Okay, I say we all just держаться together.
Tonight everyone
meet at my house.
And bring some friends. But don't tell everyone.
Try to keep it (тихий спокойный молчаливый).
Okay.
Yo ! Party at Cindy's house !
Drunk white women for everybody !
Ray, if you see Bobby,
tell him I love him.
Okay. If I see Bobby,
I'll tell him I love him.
Jesus ! It's okay. It's all right.
It's just me, baby.
What, you don't still think it's me, do you ?
No.
It's just that somebody
did try to kill me.
Yeah. And the police said I scared him away.
I know. He called me last night.
You see, it couldn't have been me.
I was in jail last night. Remember ?
You're the best.
I'm sorry.
Please understand.
Understand what ? That my girlfriend would
rather call me a killer than touch me ?
That's not true, Bobby.
(тогда потом) what is it ?
What is it ? She's gone
and she's not coming back.
It's been over a year, Cindy. But Ginger was
such an important part of the Spice Girls.
Oh, you gotta move on, baby.
Oh !
I'm sorry
if my complicated life...
is an затрудняет, беспокоит
to your perfect (существование жизнь бытие).
Cindy. Cind.
[ Sheriff ]
Okay, everybody, listen up.
Let me just say, uh,
the killing of these teenagers
has been tragic, but, uh...
Hey, you know,
shit happens.
[ Reporters Shouting ]
Sheriff ! Sheriff !
- Yes, Miss Громшторм.
- Have they found Cindy Campbell's father ?
- No.
- Isn't he a suspect ?
That is секретный information.
Where are you getting that ?
I'm sorry,
but my sources are строго секретный, Sheriff.
Hey, Gail.
Gail swallows.
Watch this.
Hello. Who is this ?
What ?
You wanna kill me ?
Oh, God. Hold on.
- Cindy, it's for you.
- [ Girls Laughing ]
All right,
(закругляться сбивать сталкивать), Buffy.
Now, as you all have heard,
there is a killer in town...
and the police просила us to give you
the следующих safety советов (чаевых).
Stay in хорошо освещен areas.
Do not travel alone
когда только possible.
Always (очистка стереть смыть) front to back.
And remember, never, ever
believe someone...
when they tell you
that shaving your лобковый hair...
will избавить you
of crab infestation.
Now, I understand this is a
difficult time for you young ladies.
So if anyone needs
to come to my office to talk,
I am here for you.
- What a (горшок духовка кастрюля) of shit.
- [ Cindy ] It's not, Buffy !
- He's real !
- [ Girls Laughing ]
[ Вдыхает ]
Miss Mann ?
Come in, dear. Have a seat.
Take off your лифчик if you'd like.
No, thanks.
What can I do for you,
Cindy ?
I need to talk.
See, I have this problem...
and I don't know
who to tell.
- Not feeling so fresh ?
- Huh ?
Feminine запах and зуд
привело тебя сюда (опустилась)?
Uh, no. No, not that.
Then what is it ?
I have a terrible secret.
Well, Cindy, we all have
our little secrets.
Sometimes we do things
we're not so гордимся.
Some for money,
others to получить the athletic (граница
преимущество) on the соревновании.
Sometimes those secrets
come back to преследовать нас.
- Aah !
- Do you know what I mean ?
Yes, I do, um, Miss Mann.
Thanks for ball...
I mean, all your help.
I have to go to class.
Anytime, dear.
Buffy, are you coming ?
я догоню with you guys in a sec.
[ Man шепот ]
Redrum.
Hello ?
Somebody there ?
Hello !
[ вздыхает]
Very funny.
Who тебя надоумил
to this, Cindy ?
Потеряй (мыс плащ накидка).
It's way (как также очень еще) '90s horror.
Oh, so what movie is this from,
Die, Cheerleader, Die ?
Wanna play psycho killer ?
Can I be the беспомощный cheerleader ?
Oh, so this is where I'm должна
была умолять for my life ?
Please, Mr Killer,
don't kill me.
So is this where
I'm supposed to bleed ?
Oh, look,
I'm bleeding !
Oh, yeah, I'm
supposed to run, right ?
Okay. I'm running !
I'm running ! Help !
Help ! Now I'm gonna fall and break my leg,
оставив me helpless.
- [ Bones треск ]
- Aah !
Вот так, Mr Scary Killer.
I'm panicking now.
Oh, God !
Somebody please help me !
Oh, God, no !
No !
Oh, now what ?
I guess this is the big кульминация.
Hope you don't mind if I симитирую it. Aah !
Oh, look at me.
I'm all dead.
I'm a противная, scary отрубленная head.
Come on. Please.
Do you know who I am ? I'm Miss Teen.
You're really giving me a головная боль.
And you got blood all over my Gucci sweater.
I hope you're gonna pay for that.
Меня не будут игнорировать подобные...
- I'm gonna jump !
- Phil, get back in there.
No !
What are you doing up there ?
- Be обоснованный.
- I can't take this fucking job...
or those (жирный, сальный)
придурочных teenagers any more !
I'm going to end it all ! Wait !
Hold on ! Мы получаем помощь для вас!
Now we know Bobby's not the killer.
So who is ?
I don't know.
If the killer was in your house last night,
why didn't he just kill you then ?
Because he's just
(издевается, портит, возится, играет) with us.
Don't you see ?
Он держит нас там, где хочет.
We can't go to the police. He's just out
there watching us and waiting for us.
What are you
waiting for, huh ?
What are you waiting for ?
What are you
waiting for ?
[ To Himself ]
What am I waiting for ?
- [ кричит ] What am I waiting for ?
- What are you waiting for ?
- Fuck you !
- [ толпа вздыхает ]
[ Woman ]
Oh, my God.
Ray, I still don't think
this party is a good idea.
You know I'm not gonna let nothin'
happen to you. I just don't feel right.
Why can't we just do something else ?
How about we go to the movies ?
Huh ? You like that ?
See a небольшой фильм, huh ?
** [ Hip Hop Plays
On Radio ]
Hey ! This is my song !
Hey !
You know they gave me a приветствие
on the album, right ? What ?
* Everywhere I go
I see the same ho's **
Ooh, Brenda.
Did I tell you how sexy you
look in my майка свитер?
I do, Ray ?
Yes.
I like it. Hey, get up.
Go over there. Let me see it.
[ хихиканье ]
Ooh !
Yes, I like that.
You like that ?
You like that ? Yeah. Hey !
- Hey, put this on with it.
- [ Laughing ]
- Ray, you are so (странный чокнутая).
- That's right. You know I'm freaky, girl.
Go on. Pull it.
Pull it up.
[ Both ] Ooh, ooh,
ooh, ooh, ah, ahh !
Yeah.
Here. Put this on with it.
Go on.
- Are you sure ?
- Go on, girl. Go on. натянуть на.
Okay.
Go on.
- I like that look.
- Ooh ! I'm bad.
Here.
Put this on with it.
Go on, girl.
Put it on.
Yeah. Put that shit on there.
Come on. Just засунуть it on.
Do it. Yeah.
Ooh, so fucking sexy.
Come here, girl. Bring your little
sexy ass over here. Come on !
Full speed. Атака (обвинение заряд плата) !
[ рычание ]
Yes ! Yes !
Come on ! Turn around !
Turn around ! Come on !
Yes, Brendan ! Take it, Brendan !
Take it, Brendan !
Who ?
Uh... Uh, Brenda.
Put the helmet on. No, let's роль-play.
Come on. You get me.
Come on ! Come on !
Huh ?
I'm here at Любовник на на шухере.
It's dark,
it's in the (середина центр) of nowhere,
and it's where hormone-driven
teens love to come and дурачиться.
So very likely we're about
to see someone get killed.
Okay, sure enough, there's a girl in that
car, блузка расстёгнута, совсем одна.
Let's see if she'll have
a word with us.
Hi. Gail (град, шквал, гроза с градом),
author of the new book You're Next.
Oh, yeah.
Can you tell us your name ?
Well, my name's Heather. Can you tell us
what you're doing out here all alone ?
Well, yeah, sure. My boyfriend and
I were just, like, целовались...
and then we heard a noise out there,
so he went to go check it,
but... well, that was,
like, ten minutes ago.
Yeah, yeah. Has it переходит your little сознание
that your boyfriend was probably murdered...
and you're about
to be убитой next ?
Really ? No way !
Way.
Heather, good luck.
Okay, thanks, Gail. You're the best.
[ Screaming ] Just as I thought.
The murder is happening пока мы говорим.
I'm going to try and ввязываться в
кровопролитие.. Are you getting this ?
Excuse me. Heather,
can you tell us what you're feeling, honey ?
Lots of pain. Gail, please help me.
Gail, please !
I'd like to help you out, kid, but it's (рейд облавa
зачисткa). Sir, sir, can I get a word with you ?
You got a lot of (наглость выдержка нервный
нерв) coming here. I'm just trying to do my job.
Get the camera off me now ! You're dead, bitch.
No, Kenny, keep сьемку (качение вращение)!
I'm gonna slice your head off and shove
it up his ass. Убири that camera off me !
Oh, my God, Kenny !
Kenny, move your fat ass !
Kenny ! Oh, my God,
he's right behind you !
[ Kenny ]
This man is преследует Miss Gail.
[ Kenny хрипит ]
[ глухой стук ]
I'm so scared right now.
I just want to say...
to the family
of my cameraman, Kenny,
I am so sorry.
This was my interview,
my story.
It's all my (вина ошибка промах дефект).
You want some popcorn ? Uh-uh.
I brought me a little snack of my own.
[ Шелест бумаги ]
You want some chicken ?
Nah.
Для всеобщего удовольствия
ПОЖАЛУЙСТА СОБЛЮДАЙТЕ МОЛЧАНИЕ (ТИШИНА)
Mm-hmm. For all y'all болтунов там in here,
it's time to keep it down right now.
Shh.
Shh, верни себе.
Shh !
Why they actin' уже ? It (ведь, ничего)
nothin' but the (предпросмотр, анонс).
Следующий ПИСАЮЩИЙ ПОКАЗ был подтвержден ТОЛЬКО
ДЛЯ НЕЗРЕЛОЙ АУДИТОРИИ. Если вы можете это прочитать,
вы слишком близко. Писать, писать, какашки, сопли, пердеж,
анус. НЕЗРЕЛЫЙ. Мы думали это было бы забавно поместить
это здесь. Поцелуй наши задницы и сними с паузы.
The largest ship
the world had ever known.
Its 400 passengers and экипаж on a первое (девичье)
путешествие (плавание) к храброму new world.
A путешествие that would change
their lives forever.
Whoo !
I'm the king of the world !
Whoo-hoo !
- [ кричит ] - [ Whipmaster ] Get
your ass back down there, boy !
I'm gonna go to the bathroom real quick.
The movie about to come on.
I gotta go to the bathroom.
Here. Take your hot sauce.
[ Brenda ] Hurry up, man.
Don't be long.
(отойти подтвердить) !
Let him through !
You can move back some.
You don't own the theatre.
[ Men болтовня ]
[ Bell Rings ] [ диктор ведущий
комментатор ] они стартовали!
It's number three in the lead.
Number two close behind.
And number three
is the winner !
Number two has placed,
and number four чтобы показать.
Next week's тройную корону
starts at 2:30.
[ капает текла ]
Be here early.
[Baby звучит похоже кажется]
[ Sounds Continue ]
[ Laughing ]
Hey, who was that ?
Go ahead.
Do it again. Do it again.
Anon.
[ Brenda ]
Mm-mmm. Mm-mmm.
Mm-mmm !
Don't go in there !
- [ Yells ] -
[ Screams ] - [ Screams ]
[ Laughing ] Lord, I'm gonna have a
heart (сердечный приступ, инфаркт)!
Man, this is
some scary shit !
Oh, I am scared !
[ Continues Laughing ]
- Excuse me.
- I think I paid my money like everybody else up in here.
- ...не в ее пользу...
- That (ведь ничего) no man.
You can see her real hair right there !
Do you возражать ?
I know you better
get outta my face !
От моего лица!
Outta my face !
This is все моё up in here.
You справиться с that.
[ Man ] Will you shut the fuck up !
[ Woman ] Yeah !
Mmm, mmm.
This movie is good.
Hey, baby.
You came back just in time.
Она собирается заняться этим
with Shakespeare.
She dressing like a man...
Shut up.
Yeah, I got you.
I got you on camera.
You on скрытая (открытый) камера now.
You ain't know that.
- [ Cell Phone писк ]
- [ Audience стонет ]
Hello. Hey, girl.
Uh-uh. I'm in the movie.
Shakespeare In Love.
Uh-uh. Ooh ! You lying.
For Christ's ради (сакэ мать память польза),
will you just shut your trap (западня капкан рот люк сети поймать)!
- Shut up !
- Hold on.
I don't know why вы все
is actin' like this.
My girlfriend already seen the movie. She said they
don't (даже ещё вообще ровно) stay together in the end.
Give me that.
Right on.
Will you sit down.
[ стонет ]
Shut up.
Your ass is обречена (трава, газон, стукач).
This is for Thelma !
And Louise !
This is for talking
through The Беглеца !
You испортила Schindler's
List. Jackie Chan movies.
Ночи в стиле буги!
And Big Momma's House !
[ Audience насмешки ]
Aaaaaahhhhh !
[ Applause ]
And I cannot marry на дочери
сэра Robert De Lesseps.
** [ громко Rock ]
Um, you guys,
there's a немного too many people.
Oh, honey, please don't бросать...
Hey, you guys, stop.
Hey ! Hey, please !
That's my папина!
No, don't touch... Ah, no !
Do you have more beer ?
Do you have more beer ? Um, yeah.
Uh, check in the garage.
No, no, no, no !
Don't !
[ Metal лязг звон ]
[ вздох ]
Kitty, you scared me.
- [ лязг звон ]
- [ ржание]
Horsey.
Oh, you scared me too.
Hello ?
Who's there ?
Oh, my God ! Oh, my God !
Please, don't !
Please !
У меня здесь только эпизод !
[ Screaming ]
Oh, my God !
(выпивать залпом, пыхтеть)! Chug ! Chug !
Chug ! Chug ! Chug ! Chug !
[ Screaming ]
[ вой ]
Yeah !
Oh, Bobby. Bobby.
I was волнуюсь about you.
I thought the killer got
to you before I могла бы.
могла бы what ?
I wanna go upstairs.
There's something I wanna show you.
[ смеется ] Yeah.
[ Chuckles ] Oh, yeah.
- Hey, party on !
- [ All ] Yeah !
So... So.
[ Хихикает ]
Here we are...
again.
Yeah.
[ Giggles ]
And, you know,
if you're not ready,
I'll understand.
Bobby.
I am ready.
You are ?
Yeah.
I can't keep fighting
these (призыв, желание, порыв).
I have to just
give in to (им, ним)...
and let them поток.
Right.
Bobby ?
Huh ?
я была so selfish.
This is like a scene
from a movie or something.
Only it isn't a movie,
Bobby.
This is real life.
It's all a movie, baby.
There's the sound guy. There's the
сценарий начальник. How you doin', baby ?
Bobby ?
What ?
What I имею в виду
is that in real life...
you have to enjoy
each moment.
[ стон стенание ]
Mmm ! Ow !
[ стон ]
Bobby.
[ бормотание ]
Bobby !
Can I tell you a secret ?
Sure, man.
I see dead people.
[ Laughing ]
Man, this shit is awesome !
Yo, son, we gotta roll
some more of that shit !
[ крики вопль ]
Ah, shit !
We don't have
any more papers, man.
any more papers.
Oh, man !
What can we use to make a (бонг кальян бом)?
затяжка ! Toke ! Toke !
Toke ! Toke ! Toke ! Toke !
Toke ! Toke ! Toke ! Toke ! Toke !
Toke ! Toke ! Toke ! Yeah !
Oh, shit, son !
Toke ! Toke ! Toke ! Toke !
This some good shit !
[крики, радостные возгласы ]
[ хрюканье ворчание хрип]
[ Grunting ]
Bobby !
I've never done this before. What ?
It's okay. It's okay.
It's just like... It's like sucking
on a Ириска Рулет Популярный.
A Tootsie Pop ?
Yeah, a вишневый-(вкус аромат) one.
Oh. With the помадка
in the middle ?
[ Makes Sucking Sound ] Okay.
[ хихикает ]
* Show me now
Show me how *
* How it feels when we're
together * Just like that.
* I'm afraid if we wait * Just like that,
baby.
* We'll be waiting до скончания мира!
** [ кризис кранч хруст ] Ah !
Oh ! Jesus !
Я не могла дождаться
to get to the жвачка middle.
You know what ?
Let me. Oh. Okay.
Goddam !
** [ Man поет,
текст неразборчивый ]
* I'm flyin' solo
but don't know if I can stop *
* Don't ask me why
Don't make me lie *
* Просто расслабься.
Просто сиди спокойно *
* Enjoy the поездкой
* 'Cause I'm a (космонавт пришелец)
[ Bats писк ]
[ Cindy Giggles ]
Guess it's been a while.
* So stay with me *
Oh ! Oops !
[ хохот ]
It's very, uh, '70s of you.
Oh, yeah.
Oh, Bobby !
[рвотные позывы]
Come here, Bobby !
I want it now !
Oh, man,
am I fuckin' (кайф обкуриться пьяный) !
Yeah,
me too, son.
Hey, you guys
hear that ?
[ Электронный звук, который предшествует
появлению убийцы ]. [хныканье]
[ Laughing ]
Oh !
[ All Laughing ]
Shh !
[ Тональные сигналы ]
- [ Line звон ]
- [ Girl ] Hello ?
- Hello. What's your favourite scary movie ?
[ All Laughing ]
Let me talk to her.
Shh !
I'm gonna выпотрошить you
like a fish !
[ All Laughing ]
Oh, yeah ! Oh !
Yeah !
What's my name, Bobby ?
What ? Ah !
- What's my name, bitch ?
- Ow ! God ! It's Cindy !
чей is it, Bobby ?
It's yours.
Ahhhhhh !
- [ рев треск ]
- Oh, my God !
[грохот урчание]
Oh, shit !
[крик]
Рэп. * Даже не спорь (соревнуйся), потому что
я заставлю тебя раздеться *
* Как порно-танцовщицы, ждущие у
парадной двери ответа *
* Эй, йо, меня тошнит от искусственных
МК like silicone titties *
Hey, yo, check it, yo.
* Трахаться с дешевым мячом
* I wanna smoke
Чич и Чонг *
* And if I wanna fuck long I let my
(вмятинадинь)-a-long удар по бонгу *
* А затем песня всегда
передает дуэт влево *
* Because the right way
is wrong * [ кудахтанье ]
Whoo-hoo ! I got one. I got one.
Here it goes. Ready ?
* I'm gonna глубокая рана and глубокая рана
Cut another hole in your ass *
* I пролить blood on the walls
then play tennis with your balls *
* If the phone rings
don't answer the call *
* Gonna порезать your горло
fuck you like a goat *
* шкурка your крайняя плоть снять
and make a зимнее пальто ** мир !
Yo !
That was the улетная рифма I ever seen,
son !
Bobby...
where were you tonight ?
What ?
I was just любопытно.
What took you so long
to get here ?
Why you so curious ?
I don't know.
I thought it would соответствовать
the '90s horror cliche...
if you оказалось
to be the killer.
Oh, so, what ? You think
I killed Buffy and Greg ?
Buffy and Greg are dead ?
I thought you knew that.
Oh, my God !
Bobby, turn around !
It's the killer !
[ Screaming ]
Cindy !
[задыхается]
Oh, my God ! Bobby !
Bobby ! Cindy. Help me.
Bobby, it's okay.
Gimme the gun. Gimme...
It's gonna be okay, Bobby.
Yo, wait for me !
There's a killer in the house !
There's ass, blood
and guts everywhere !
Someone done gone crazy,
son !
[ хихиканье ] We all go a little
crazy sometimes. Bobby, no !
Oh, shit, son !
[ хныканье ]
Oh, my God !
[ стон ]
Cindy, he shot me
in the легкие.
[вдыхание]
You wanna hit this shit ?
Ketchup.
Just like my mom puts on
her spaghetti, baby.
Oh, my God ! Ray, you've gotta help me !
Bobby's gone crazy !
[ Girl's Voice ]
Surprise !
[ Killer's Voice ] Surprise, Cindy !
[ задыхается ]
Why are you doing this,
Bobby ?
Why ? Why ?
You hear that, Ray ?
I think she wants
a (мотив причина повод стимул).
Did Scream have a (сюжет заговор
участок план график кладбище)? No.
[ смеется ] Did I Know What You
Did Last Summer make any sense ?
Don't think so !
What about the (продолжение сиквел)?
What was with that fat, white Jamaican kid ?
-I wanna kill that motherfucker.
-It was bad casting, Bobby.
How about this for a motive ?
отсутствие нехватка of sex !
It can cause serious
отклонение от норм поведения.
- I thought you loved me.
- Oh, I did, baby.
I did. But (воздержание абстиненция) can
make you discover new things about yourself.
That's right, Cindy.
I'm gay.
And in случае (место дело ситуация иск
связи) you haven't заметила, so is Ray.
What ? I (am not; are not; is not.) gay.
- What are you talking about ? You took me to that club.
- So, they play good music.
- What about our trip to San Francisco, then ?
- I wanted to go shopping.
But you made love to me. No.
First of all, you sucked my...
независимо от, Ray !
I don't want to talk about this now.
дело в том, I'm a new man, and I'm ready to
оставить all this behind and start a new life.
So you killed all your friends ?
Oh, no.
Just you.
And maybe Shorty, but that
wasn't planned or anything.
But here's
the genius part.
We're подражание a serial
killer который already exists.
- It's the perfect преступление, Cindy.
- But wait ! There's more !
Hang on to your место, baby,
'cause this one's a крикун!
I'll be back.
Uh-oh.
Move your big ass.
Come on.
- Dad !
- [хрипит ворчание]
What are you gonna do,
подставить (рама кадр) him ?
Nah. We're just havin'
a little часть of fun with old папулей.
The police are gonna find
you and daddy both dead,
and me and Ray are the only
survivors of a maniac's отмщение.
You ready ? I'm ready. You ready ?
I'm ready to do this shit.
Come on. Come on.
All right. All right.
- Come on ! [крики]
- Give it to me. No !
Wait, wait, wait, wait.
Ready ? All right. Let's do this.
Wait, wait. Ready.
Come on. Come on.
Ready.
Give it to me !
No ! Wait, wait,
wait, wait, wait !
Remember what we talked about ?
To the (сторона бок). I know.
How many times we gonna go over this ?
Okay.
Stop. Just... All right.
Trust me, okay ?
All right. I'm ready. Trust me.
I got this shit. Ready ?
Wait, wait, wait !
I'm about to cut your горло, boy !
Stop действовать like a little girl.
Come on. Come on !
You're right, you're right, you're right.
Yeah, come on ! Come on. You ready ?
No !
You guys are psychos !
You've seen
one too many TV shows !
No ! Watching television shows
doesn't create psycho killers !
отмена TV shows
does !
The Wayans Brothers
was a good show, man !
It was a good-ass show,
and we didn't even get a final episode !
Take it easy ! I'm feelin'
a little дурно here !
It's my turn.
Give me the knife.
Fuck outta here.
Ain't nobody ножевое ранение me.
[ Cindy Screams ]
[ Ray, Bobby Стонет ]
Surprise, Cindy !
[Крики]
[ Growling ]
[ рычание, крик ]
[ Cindy Screams ]
стон
All right, all right.
Hold on a second.
Just give me a moment.
Ah. One...
хрип, вздох
[ Bones треск ]
Oh, yeah. That's it.
Ah. Okay.
[ Cindy кричит
** [ ирландская джига Plays ]
[ крики ]
[ Screams ]
Dad !
[ бормочет, задыхается]
Are you okay ?
I thought I told you not to
have a party unless I was here.
But, Dad, you were here. You were in
the (шкаф чулан кладовка гардероб).
Oh, yeah, that's right. Did you get
some girlfriends' numbers for me ?
Dad, they're dead.
Ah, you know, I can't (справится, перерыв).
[ Siren вой ] What's that ?
Is that the cops ?
Okay, okay, listen, honey.
Help me up now.
Uh... Uh... If the cops come,
tell 'em I'm a сантехник, okay ?
You had a протекающий кран, and you called, and
they sent me over. We don't know each other.
[ Sirens Continue ]
No ! No !
[ шины визжат]
Dad, Dad,
put your arms down.
What the hell's goin' on here ? [ Man ]
Sheriff, it's a (кровавая баня, боиня) in there.
He was right here !
I swear it ! Who was ?
The killer !
The guy that murdered all my friends !
And the sick bastard planted
drugs all in the house there.
All over the place.
Dad. Stop it.
All right, Cindy. I'm gonna have
to take you down to the station.
I'm cool, though, right ?
I'm okay ?
Let's... Let's go, Cindy.
Cindy.
Call me.
Daddy'll
get you out, honey.
Okay. Let's go
over this again.
You say it was an accident.
Yes.
- He was on the road.
- And you think he came back to get (реванш отмщение) ?
It has to be him, Sheriff.
[ стук стучать ]
Here, Sheriff.
They wanted me to give this to you.
- That'll be all, Doofy.
- Okay.
I'm gonna go, then.
All right. All right.
Bye, Cind.
I'm sorry, Cindy.
It wasn't the man you guys killed.
His name was David Keegan. Some fishermen
found his body a few weeks later.
- He's (захоронен закопан) in Lakewood Кладбище.
- That's impossible.
- Then I don't know who it could be.
- He's (должен придется обязан) be someone...
who was connected with all the victims,
someone who knew about the accident.
Someone who could move around
without being замечаным отметил.
Oh, my God.
She used to baby-sit my brother Doofy.
He had the biggest crush on her.
задыхаясь
It's me, Cind.
'Night, Cind.
- Doofy !
- придурок засранец ?
Have you seen Doofy ?
No.
Have you seen Doofy? No, Sheriff.
Has anybody seen Doofy ?
No. [ Man ] Yeah.
Just went out the back, Sheriff.
[ Sheriff ]
Doofy !
* He walks alone
under the big city lights *
* He always knows
just when the time is right *
* He never shows what he's
thinking He keeps it inside *
* Because he's
too cool for school *
*  Он оживает
when the sun goes down *
* Он все правильно понимает
You know he's always внизу *
* He's got one eye open
and his и ухо до земли *
* And he's too cool for school
* He's an (оператор связист делец машинист телефонист)
He's a real player *
* And if you mess with him you know
you'll never win ** [ вздыхает вздохи ]
No-o-o-o-o !
** [ Song Continues, Lyrics неясный
размытый] [ Continues крик кричать ]
[ кудахтанье ] Shit, son.
Yo, what the deal ?
Yo, if y'all watchin'
this tape right now,
that means
I didn't make it.
(либо или) I'm a prisoner,
or worse, dead.
But (либой) way it goes, I'm gonna tell you
all the rules to survive this situation.
Rule number one:
You gotta be quick.
Rule number two:
Don't fall down.
And rule number three:
Whatever you do, never look back.
Y'all wish me luck.
схватить похитить and run, y'all !
Come back here, you (ублюдков
уёбков засранцы) ! Son of a bitch !
** [ Rap, невнятно неразборчивые ]
This isn't easy for me.
I know we've been
together a long time,
but I found somebody else.
Okay ? I'm in love.
Don't look at me like that !
[насморк, шмыгает носом]
We could still be friends.
You can come into my room
whenever you want.
We just can't... No.
No !
Okay, just one time.
[ жужжание шумит ]
Yeah. That's it !
Whoo ! Oh !
[ (жидкость флюид) Being всасывается ]
[ Doofy задыхается ]
[ Vacuum Stops ]